<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Denis Labrecque</title>
    <link>http://denislabrecque.ca/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Denis Labrecque</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 18:05:29 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://denislabrecque.ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Scale Air Apparel</title>
      <link>http://denislabrecque.ca/graphics/scale-air-apparel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 18:05:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://denislabrecque.ca/graphics/scale-air-apparel/</guid>
      <description>This apparel was created and branded for the Ad Design campaign of Scale Air, a model airplane show in Montreal. It is designed to be sold as a fundraiser at the event. It was first sketched out on paper, then made in Illustrator and mocked up in Photoshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asian Garden</title>
      <link>http://denislabrecque.ca/graphics/asian-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 18:04:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://denislabrecque.ca/graphics/asian-garden/</guid>
      <description>I created this scene to challenge myself to represent nature. It taught me how to use software light, and how to texture natural elements like water to make a good-looking render. An asset software called Bridge helped speed the composition process, and the image was rendered from Blender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Receptus Application</title>
      <link>http://denislabrecque.ca/programming/receptus-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 16:01:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://denislabrecque.ca/programming/receptus-application/</guid>
      <description>A fast, offline Bible browser that allows easy reading and search. Includes the King James Version, Young&amp;rsquo;s Literal Translation, Louis Segond, and French Darby translations of the Bible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warglobe Game</title>
      <link>http://denislabrecque.ca/programming/warglobe-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 15:59:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://denislabrecque.ca/programming/warglobe-game/</guid>
      <description>Eventually, Warglobe is to become an independently developed, free-to-play game with online combat in ships, airplanes, and vehicles. If possible, players will command groups of vehicles as well as drive them, combining the action and speed of a first-person shooter with the tactics of a real-time strategy game. Nevertheless, this depends on all previous phases (prototype, mission-based, and online multiplayer) being completed first.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
