<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Programming on </title>
    <link>/programming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Programming on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Waypoint Tool</title>
      <link>/programming/bing-api-map-waypoint-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/programming/bing-api-map-waypoint-tool/</guid>
      <description>This tool was created with the purpose of programming a vehicle to follow waypoints using an Arduino microcontroller paired to a GPS module.
To make editing easier, use the full-page view.
Creating and Loading Waypoints  To create a waypoint path: click on the map. To remove a waypoint: click on the waypoint and click remove. To move a waypoint: click and drag it. To save or erase coordinates: right-click the map; the location name is the point of interest nearest to the first waypoint, and that is the file&amp;rsquo;s default name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Receptus Application</title>
      <link>/programming/receptus-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 16:01:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/programming/receptus-application/</guid>
      <description>Receptus is a fast, offline Bible browser that allows easy reading and search. Includes the King James Version, Young&#39;s Literal Translation, Louis Segond, and French Darby translations of the Bible.
The code for this app was written by Denis from December 2019 to January 2020. To see this app&#39;s source code, visit the GitHub repository. Contributions to the app&#39;s code are welcome.
Key FeaturesTabbed interface. Like a browser, this Bible app is able to load many pages at once, allowing quick skipping between passages and versions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warglobe Game</title>
      <link>/programming/warglobe-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 15:59:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/programming/warglobe-game/</guid>
      <description>About the Game In the early 2000s, video games came in cereal boxes. An example of this is Battleship: Surface Thunder, a simple mission-based third-person shooter that put my child fingers in control of a battleship. I was hooked.
Since then, the distant idea of creating a game with air and naval combat has stuck. Unfortunately, many games today are based on a flat map, which is great for game engines, but not so great for players who want a larger area.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
