<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Waypoint Tool</title>
      <link>/programming/bing-api-map-waypoint-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/programming/bing-api-map-waypoint-tool/</guid>
      <description>This tool was created with the purpose of programming a vehicle to follow waypoints using an Arduino microcontroller paired to a GPS module.
To make editing easier, use the full-page view.
Creating and Loading Waypoints  To create a waypoint path: click on the map. To remove a waypoint: click on the waypoint and click remove. To move a waypoint: click and drag it. To save or erase coordinates: right-click the map; the location name is the point of interest nearest to the first waypoint, and that is the file&amp;rsquo;s default name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>North American Morgan 40&#39; Sailboat</title>
      <link>/graphics/morgan-40-sailboat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 18:05:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/graphics/morgan-40-sailboat/</guid>
      <description>These renders were made for a client who wanted to renovate his sailboat. If you are interested in similar renderings for your project, please contact Denis.
Bow master sleeping area Galley accommodations Navigation area Work area, which can still be used as a bed space Created and rendered using Blender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spenser House</title>
      <link>/graphics/spenser-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 18:05:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/graphics/spenser-house/</guid>
      <description>Creating 3D models is a skill I developed personally during college. Using rendering engines taught me the complicated but fascinating process of elaborating geometry and shaders to replicate the real world, from painstakingly copying building plans to properly using assets.
Kitchen Living room Portico Exterior Designed by architect Guy Peterson, Spenser House is a residence made in the Sarasota School of Architecture’s signature style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern Home</title>
      <link>/graphics/modern-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 15:49:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/graphics/modern-home/</guid>
      <description>Front view Two stone block towers support this house, giving it the feeling of floating above ground. The main living spaces are left open plan, with large windowed walls funneling views towards both the front and the back, helping maintain privacy. The windows are also placed to provide features at night, where they will glow brightly against the dark stone construction, enhancing the building’s volume.
Rooftop terrace Requested spaces for this house were: a living area with kitchen, a balcony, and a central courtyard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 21:51:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>SubjectMessageSendThanks! Sent to your email program.
let div_container = document.querySelector(&#39;div.contact-content&#39;)let fld_subject = document.querySelector(&#39;#subjectField&#39;)let txt_message = document.querySelector(&#39;#messageField&#39;)let btn_send = document.querySelector(&#39;#sendEmail&#39;)let div_confirmation = document.querySelector(&#39;div.circle__box&#39;)function sendEmail() {let mail = document.createElement(&#34;a&#34;)mail.href = &#39;mailto:denis.g.labrecque@gmail.com?subject=&#39; + encodeURIComponent(fld_subject.value) + &#39;&amp;body=&#39; + encodeURIComponent(txt_message.value)mail.click();div_confirmation.classList.remove(&#39;hidden&#39;)div_container.style.display = &#39;none&#39;}AboutWhen he was very young, Denis enjoyed drawing airplanes and rolling a miniature steam engine around to understand how the wheels paired together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Résumé</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 21:51:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>EducationPensacola Christian College, FloridaB.S. in Computing: Information TechnologyB.S. in Visual Arts: Graphic DesignAugust 2015—December 2020 (December graduate); GPA 3.6/4.0
Lead a small team of designers to create a student publication, following business requirements.
Helped lead seven team members to code an online testing software in Oracle and ASP.NET, using effective communication to put the project back on track and deliver on time.
Work ExperienceIT at Pensacola Christian College, FloridaWeb Developer2019, 2020 (seasonal)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scale Air Campaign</title>
      <link>/graphics/scale-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 18:05:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/graphics/scale-air/</guid>
      <description>This advertising campaign is for an imaginary model aircraft meetup in Montreal. It supports the event’s design needs, and is meant to attract visitors. Because of its particular location, part of the campaign is bilingual.
Apparel This apparel is designed to be sold as a fundraiser at the event. It was first sketched out on paper, then made in Illustrator and mocked up in Photoshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asian Garden</title>
      <link>/graphics/asian-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 18:04:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/graphics/asian-garden/</guid>
      <description>I created this scene to challenge myself to represent nature. It taught me how to use software light, and how to texture natural elements like water to make a good-looking render. An asset software called Bridge helped speed the composition process, and the image was rendered from Blender.
Early on, the details are blocked in, but the lighting needs work. The fireflies are from a non-denoised draft render in Cycles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Receptus Application</title>
      <link>/programming/receptus-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 16:01:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/programming/receptus-application/</guid>
      <description>Receptus is a fast, offline Bible browser that allows easy reading and search. Includes the King James Version, Young&#39;s Literal Translation, Louis Segond, and French Darby translations of the Bible.
The code for this app was written by Denis from December 2019 to January 2020. To see this app&#39;s source code, visit the GitHub repository. Contributions to the app&#39;s code are welcome.
Key FeaturesTabbed interface. Like a browser, this Bible app is able to load many pages at once, allowing quick skipping between passages and versions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warglobe Game</title>
      <link>/programming/warglobe-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 15:59:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/programming/warglobe-game/</guid>
      <description>About the Game In the early 2000s, video games came in cereal boxes. An example of this is Battleship: Surface Thunder, a simple mission-based third-person shooter that put my child fingers in control of a battleship. I was hooked.
Since then, the distant idea of creating a game with air and naval combat has stuck. Unfortunately, many games today are based on a flat map, which is great for game engines, but not so great for players who want a larger area.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>